ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Women in 'Labor' Bear New Fruits, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Chicago Daily Defender. December 10, 1977
- Two Articles from The Washington Star and The News (Mexico City), 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: NLRB Seeking to Enjoin Anti-Union Textile Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Washington Star.. December 1, 1977
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union sued, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 11)
    The News (Mexico City). November 10, 1977
- U.S. Injunction Against Stevens?, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Time Magazine. December 12, 1977
- Two Articles from the New Bern Sun-Journal and the News and Observer, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Don't Subsidize Anti-Union Sentiment, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 13)
    News and Observer. December 12, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Paves Labor's Way, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 13)
    New Bern Sun-Journal December 2, 1977
- Union Begins Boycott Battle, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Southern Textile News. December 13, 1977
- Stevens Agrees to Pay, Rehire Dismissed Worker, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Daily News Record. December 13, 1977
- NLRB Opens Hearings: Stevens to Rehire Worker, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 16)
  The News and Observer. December 16, 1977
- Two Articles from the AFL-CIO Milwaukee Labor Press and the Galesburg Labor Press, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Milwaukee Boycott Urged On J. P. Stevens Products, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 17)
    AFL-CIO Milwaukee Labor Press. December 23, 1976
  - Item 2: New Charges Against J. P. Stevens Co., 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Galesburg Labor News. December 16, 1976
- Two Articles from the Missouri Council of Churches News and unknown., 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Anti-Union J. P. Stevens Boycotted: Help of Teamsters Sought, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Effect of the 1976 Election on Congress, News clipping (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Missouri Council of Churches News. December 1976
- Southern Leaders Form Group to Support Stevens Textile Workers, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 19)
  New York Times. December 18, 1976
- Two Articles from the Danville Register and the Sanford Herald, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Incident at Princeton, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Danville Register. December 22, 1976
  - Item 2: Southern Leaders Back Stevens Workers, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Sanford Herald. December 19, 1976
- Stevens Goods Still Sold, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 21)
  December 19, 1977.
- Target: The South, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 22)
  The Richmond News Leader. December 22, 1977
- Catholic Appalachia Unit Meets: Textile Industry Talks Urged, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Catholic Sun. December 22, 1976
- Stevens' White Sale Target of Leaflets, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Detroit Labor News. December 23, 1976
- Hospital Workers at J. P. Stevens Rally, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Public Employee Press. December 9, 1977
- Two Articles from the Record Forum, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: National Council of Churches Endorses J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Record Forum. December 1977
  - Item 2: U.S.-Japanese Textile Unions Unite In Fight For Fair Trade, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Big Southern Textile Mill Loses Major Labor Case, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Las Vegas Sun. December 29, 1977
- Union Gains at J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 28)
  The Evening Bulletin. December 29, 1977
- Textile Firm Bargained In 'Bad Faith', Must Pay All Costs, Judge Rules, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 29)
  The Washington Star. December 29, 1977
- Ruling Against Stevens May Aid Textile Unon, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Anderson Independent. December 30, 1977
- ACTWU Official Hails Latest NLRB Ruling, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. December 29, 1977
- Labor On The Southern Front: New Tactics In The Textile War, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 32)
  The Nation. December 10, 1977
- Is This Short Cut Necessary?, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Chicago Tribune. December 3, 1977
- U.S. Warns Stevens Of Court Action, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 34)
  The Charlotte Observer. December 1, 1977
- Reining In Stevens: Again, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Chattanooga Daily Times. January 2, 1978
- Quinn Opposes Union Training Center, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 36)
  January 5. 1978.
- Stevens, Scofflaw, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Des Moines Tribune. January 5, 1978
- The Right-to-Work Fad, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 38)
  The New Republic. January 7, 1978
- The Aftermath of a Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Miami Review and Daily Record. January 10, 1978
- Farah Co., 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Hornell Tribune. January 10, 1978
- Clothing Workers Union Disputes Lesher's Claims, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Worth Citizen. January 12, 1978
- Rabbinical Association Joins J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Jewish Light. January 18, 1978
- Labor-Law Catalyst, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Cedar Rapids Gazette. January 19, 1978
- Court Warns J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 44)
  The Atlanta Journal. January 20, 1978
- How To Use Labour Laws, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 45)
  The Economist. January 21, 1978
- Local UFW Supporters Outline Textile Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Daily Cardinal. January 25, 1978
- The Stevens-Labor Battle: Long and Bitter, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Women's Wear Daily. January 25, 1978
- Stevens Guilty Of 'Bad Faith' Bargaining In Roanoke Rapids, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Indianapolis Leader. January 31, 1978
- Stevens Loses Two Battles, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 49)
  This Week. January 28, 1978
- Anti-J. P. Stevens Rally Set Saturday, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Birmingham Post-Herald. January 21, 1978
- Unionists Will Rally, March To Support Boycott Of Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 51)
  The Birmingham News. January 20, 1978
- Court Finds Textile Firm In Contempt, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Unions Are Now Attacking The South, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Gatesville Index. January 18, 1978
- Treasury Department Sets Floor: Steelworkers Waiting To See Impact Of 'Trigger' Prices, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Press Associates. January 18, 1978
- Stevens vs. Union: Bishops Take Role In Labor Dispute, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 55)
  The Atlanta Journal. January 5, 1978
- Textile Boycott Launched, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 56)
  Hamilton Ontario Spectator. February 15, 1978
- Senate Panels Open Hearings On Revised Employment Bill, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 57)
  The Washington Post. February 3, 1978
- Textile Union Presses Boycott Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 58)
  The San Diego Union. February 9, 1978
- Cornell Students Organize To Boycott J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 59)
  Cornell Sun. February 10, 1978
- Baseball's Hank Aaron Joins Textile's Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Manchester Union Leader. February 10, 1978
- We Ring Avon's Bells Over Ties To Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 61)
  Public Employee Press. February 10, 1978
- Stevens Annual Meeting To Be Here, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 62)
  The Greenville News. February 15, 1978
- Churches Join Textile Fray, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 63)
  The Sacramento Bee. February 18, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Loses Appeal In Anti-Union Tactics Case, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 64)
  The Boston Globe. February 22, 1978
- Athletes Endorse Stevens Boycott: Aaron Hammers J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 65)
  Racine Labor. February 24, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Denies Anti-Union Claims, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 66)
  Greenfield Recorder. February 27, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Loses Union Test In High Court, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 67)
  Philadelphia Inquirer. February 22, 1978
- Stevens Workers Want Debate, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 68)
  Greenville Piedmont. February 20, 1978
- The Day The Sun Vanished, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 69)
  The Boston Globe. February 17, 1978
- Athletes Endorse Stevens Boycott: Aaron Hammers J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 70)
  Kenosha Labor. February 9, 1978
- Stevens Asked To Debate Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 71)
  Greenville News. February 9, 1978
- How Anti-Union Employers Harass Workers, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 72)
  White Collar. March 1978
- Union Official Sees Stevens Boycott Success, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 73)
  Greenville Piedmont. March 6, 1978
- For fifteen years now, the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union has been fighting, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 74)
  Burrelle's TV Clips. March 8, 1978
- Pointless Meeting, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 75)
  Waltersboro Press and Standard. March 9, 1978
- NAACP Supports Union Effort At Eno Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 76)
  The News of Orange County. March 9, 1978
- Firm's Chief Kicked Off Bank Board: Textile Workers Press Campaign Against J. P. Stevens In South, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Bishops Rebuke J. P. Stevens For Anti-Union Stand, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 78)
  The Detroit News. March 15, 1978
- Stevens Company Silent On NLRB Pact Rumor, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 79)
  Newsday (Long Island). March 16, 1978
- Boycott Endorsement Withheld: Bishops Call Stevens Co. To Neutrality, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 80)
  The Pilot. March 17, 1978
- Two Articles from the Anderson Daily Mail and The Greenville News, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Stevens Says Criticism Unfair, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 81)
    Anderson Daily Mail. March 16, 1978
  - Item 2: Women To Back Labor at Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 81)
    The Greenville News. March 17, 1978
- Company Side, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 82)
  The News-Times. March 18, 1978
- Stevens Faces New Pressure, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 83)
  Anderson Independent. March 18, 1978
- Brown Lung in the Cotton Mills, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 84)
  America. March 18, 1978
- Southern Bishops Address Labor Controversy, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 85)
  North Carolina Catholic. March 19, 1978
- Our Meddling Bishops, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Return of the Native, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 87)
  The Greensboro Record. March 22, 1978
- Avon Chief Bows To Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 88)
  Daily News. March 22, 1978
- Avon's Chairman Resigns From Board of Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 89)
  Daily News Record. March 22, 1978
- Reinstated Worker Hopes He Helped Union Cause, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 90)
  The News and Observer. March 28, 1978
- Fired JPS Worker Back Under Court Order, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 91)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. March 28, 1978
- Stevens Dares Union To Hold 'Fair' Elections, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 92)
  Greenville News. March 29, 1978
- Union Pressure Rising, Chamber Speaker Warns, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 93)
  Kingsport Times. March 30, 1978
- Hold Stevens' Election, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 94)
  Waterbury Republican. March 30, 1978
- The Union and The Mills, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 95)
  The Greensboro Record. March 31, 1978
- Stevens Dares Union To Hold Secret Vote, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 96)
  Columbia State. March 31, 1978
- Worker Encouraged By What He Found On Return To JPS Job, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 97)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. March 29, 1978
- Secret Balloting Called For In JPS Ad, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 98)
- Union Blackmail, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 99)
  Winchester Star. March 28, 1978
- Wallace Plant To Get Union Despite Vote, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 100)
  March 27, 1978.
- Responding to pressures of a union campaign, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 101)
  The Trib. March 22, 1978
- Union Scores Second Victory at Stevens, As Avon Chairman Resigns From Board, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 102)
  The Wall Street Journal. March 22, 1978
- A Gathering Momentum Against J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 103)
  Business Week. March 20, 1978
- Today Manny Hanny, Tomorrow The World?, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 104)
  Forbes. March 20, 1978
- Union Objects To Report, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 105)
  Greenville News. March 16, 1978
- Stevens And Union Both Got Their Licks In, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 106)
  The Charlotte Observer. March 12, 1978
- The Brown-Lung Controversy, 1978; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 107)
  Columbia Journalism Review. March/April 1978
- Administration Backs Textile Interests, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Greenville News. April 19, 1978
- The Fabric Of Justice: Churches Vs. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Sun. April 1, 1978
- Women Join Boycott Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 3)
  The Boston Globe. April 1, 1978
- Union Money Talks On Policy Issues, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 4)
  The Buffalo Evening News. April 1, 1978
- That's Fair Enough, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Columbus Telegram. April 8, 1978
- Election At Stevens Can't Be Fair, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Waterbury Republican. April 8, 1978
- Down In Iradell: Strange New World, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 7)
  April 12, 1978.
- Latest Action Adds to Paper Overflow, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Lauringburg Exchange. April 12, 1978
- Financial Hard Times Hits Apparel Industry, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Tinley Park Southtown Economist. April 12, 1978
- The Boycott Weapon, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Bremerton Sun. April 13, 1978
- American Enka Receives NLRB Ruling, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Haywood Enterprise. April 13, 1978
- No Secret Vote, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Marlboro Herald Advocate. April 13, 1978
- Free Enterprise?, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 13)
  The News American. April 14, 1978
- Officer Elections, Taylor Law Dominate '78 RA, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 14)
  NYSUT RA78. April 17, 1978
- Textile Workers Approved New Three-Year Contract, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Willimantic Chronicle. April 17, 1978
- Union Says Fair Vote Impossible At Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 16)
  The News and Observer. April 18, 1978
- Betting On Employees, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Colorado Springs Gazette Telegraph. April 18, 1978
- Textile Leaders Unconvinced After White House Meeting, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Columbia State. April 19, 1978
- That's Fair Enough, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Lima News. April 19, 1978
- U.S. Labor, Industry, Hurt by Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Victor Riesel. April 19, 1978
- The Way It Works: Union Voters Oppose, But Bureaucrat Reverses, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Shelbyville Times-Gazette. April 19, 1978
- Labor Award Dinner, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 22)
  The Times Record. April 19, 1978
- Facts and Opinions, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Newkirk Herald Journal. April 20, 1978
- Under the Dome, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 24)
  The News and Observer. April 19, 1978
- Union Raps Firm's Record, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Wilmington Star. April 19, 1978
- Six Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Church Groups Claim Futility With Textile Firm, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    The Birmingham News. April 20, 1978
  - Item 2: Methodist Women Join J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    The Charlotte Observer. April 13, 1978
  - Item 3: Methodist Women's Group Backs Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    The New York Times. April 12, 1978
  - Item 4: N.J. Clergymen Aid Textile Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    The Record. April 20, 1978
  - Item 5: Statement By Religious Leaders Regarding J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    April 19, 1978.
  - Item 6: Women's Division, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Board of Global Ministries, United Methodist Church. April 9, 1978
- Swinging In The Opposite Direction, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Keene Valley Sun. April 20, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Settles With Labor Board On Antiunion Acts, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 28)
  The New York Times. April 29, 1978
- Fanatics Have a Role: They Make Us Aware, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 29)
  The Charlotte News. April 20, 1978
- Big Labor vs. J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Human Events. April 22, 1978
- The Stevens Boycott Is Union Intimidation, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 31)
  The Cincinnati Enquirer. April 23, 1978
- Carter's Column, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Tabor City Tribune. April 26, 1978
- Jobless Lobby in Capital, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 33)
  The Evening Bulletin. April 26, 1978
- New Market: Tar Heel Firms Enjoy Irish Success, News clipping (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Greensboro Daily News.
- Stevens Settles With NLRB, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 35)
  New York Daily News. April 29, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Promises To Halt Anti-Union Activities, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Florence Morning News. April 29, 1978
- Beerman To Shun Stevens Products, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Dayton Journal Herald. April 21, 1978
- Labor's Blacklist, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 38)
  April 20, 1978.
- Stevens Whipping Boy For Organized Labor, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 39)
  The Mobile Register. April 20, 1978
- Arrogant Leaders Hurt Union Cause, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Spring Hope Enterprise. April 20, 1978
- ACTWU Replies To JPS's Ad, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. April 17, 1978
- Stop Breaking The Law, J. P. Stevens... And Then We'll Take It To A Vote, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 42)
  The Charlotte Observer. April 14, 1978
- Stevens Officials Fight Back, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Greer Citizen. April 5, 1978
- The Questinable Stevens Ruling, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 44)
  La Grange News. April 3, 1977
- Washington Diarist: Snubbing the Socialists, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 45)
  New Republic. April 1, 1978
- Unfinished Business: The Controversial Cotton Tale, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Columbia Journalism Review. May/June 1978
- Coming Attractions, 1984, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 47)
  Hammond Star. May 1, 1978
- Mills and Unions: A Look At Proposed Legislation and Organizing Tactics, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 48)
  Rug and Carpet Industry. May 1978
- Consent Agreement: J. P. Stevens Yields To Injunction Terms, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 49)
  AFL-CIO News. May 6, 1978
- Textile Union Fight: Two Lessons From History, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 50)
  The News and Observer. May 7, 1978
- The Diary Of A Union Organizer, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 51)
  The Charlotte Observer. May 7, 1978
- Synagogues Here Take No Action, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 52)
  The Greensboro Record. May 10, 1978
- Union Left Bad Impression, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 53)
  Milledgeville Union Recorder. May 11, 1978
- Stevens Says It Didn't Do It, But It Won't Do It Any More, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 54)
  Northern California Labor. May 12, 1978
- George Meany met with the President this week, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 55)
  Burrelle's TV Clips. May 13, 1978
- Bill Duchessi's Respected, Influential and Amsterdam Seeks Native's Help, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 56)
  Schenectady Gazette. May 15, 1978
- Marshall Mounts Sharp Attack On Foes of Labor Law Revision, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 57)
  The Washington Post. May 18, 1978
- Sunbelt Strategy for United Church of Christ, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 58)
  Blackwell Times Record. May 19, 1978
- Letter to the Editor: Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 59)
  Martinsville Bulletin. May 21, 1978
- Winner Over J. P. Stevens 'Can't Afford To Go Back', 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 60)
  Danbury News-Times. May 22, 1978
- Martin To Fight Court Order, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 61)
  Martinsville Bulletin. May 24, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Challenges Union to a Companywide Vote, News clipping (Box 6, Folder 62)
  The Atlanta Journal.
- Reception Mixed For 1st Union Organizers At J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 63)
  The Charlotte Observer. May 26, 1978
- Two Articles from The Washington Post., 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: NLRB Aides Rap Textile Union on Stevens Accord, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 64)
    The Washington Post. May 26, 1978
  - Item 2: Under Court Order, Union Organizers Enter Stevens Plant for First Time, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 64)
- The Battle Continues: Stevens-Board Pact 'An Empty Promise', 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 65)
  AFL-CIO News. May 20, 1978
- Labor's Pariah, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 66)
  National Review. May 26, 1978
- NLRB Judge Reverses Illegal Stevens Firings, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 67)
  AFL-CIO News. May 27, 1978
- ACTWU Organizers Enter Stevens Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 68)
  Press Associates. May 29, 1978
- Pastor: Church Shouldn't Take Sides In Labor Fight, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 69)
  The Charlotte News. May 31, 1978
- Stevens' Labor Abuses Shock Waverly Workers, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 70)
  Palmyra Courier- Journal. May 31, 1978
- Corporate Assaults on Worker Rights Spur Labor's Boycott Campaign: J. P. Stevens Only One Example, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 71)
  UA Journal. May 1978
- Rally Against Stevens Co. Set, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 72)
  Birmingham Post-Herald. May 5, 1978
- Has J. P. Stevens Seen the Light?, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 73)
  The News and Observer. May 6, 1978
- Union Vows No 'Free Ride' For Sunbelt Industry, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 74)
  The Miami News. May 9, 1978
- Businessman Emphasizes Training: Nonunion Labor Discussed as Lure, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 75)
  The Atlanta Journal. May 9, 1978
- An Agreement Is A Compromise, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 76)
  Clothes. May 15, 1978
- Stevens Names 2 Directors, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 77)
  The Charlotte Observer. May 19, 1978
- Goal for Labor, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 78)
  The Atlanta Journal. May 18, 1978
- Will J. P. Stevens Throw in the Towel?, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 79)
  Seven Days. May 19, 1978
- Organizers Visit Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 80)
  Greenville Piedmont. May 25, 1978
- Union Organizers Allowed In Stevens Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Union-Stevens Fight at Wallace Tied Up On Appeal, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 82)
  The News and Observer. May 29, 1978